我自己在家里
So I'm in my apartment
填《肥皂剧文摘》的字谜游戏
doing the Soap Opera Digest crossword puzzle...
你猜谁是纵三的字谜提示
...and guess who is the clue for three down?
纵三  《我们的日子》空格·崔比安尼
Three down, "Days of Our Lives star, blank Tribbiani."
是我  我是空格
That's me! I'm blank!
太酷了  我们认识纵三
How cool is this! We know three down.
我在碰纵三
I'm touching three down.
没错  宝贝
Yeah, you are, baby.
纵三知道我结婚了
Three down knows I'm married.
纵三在做什么
What's three down doing?
他们有通知你上了杂志吗
So do they call to tell you your name's gonna be in this?
没有  他们杂志很喜欢我
No. They really like me over there.
想找我做人物专访  我拒绝了
They wanted to do a big profile on me, but I said no.
为什么
Why'd you say no?
还记得我上次接受采访的结果吗
Remember what happened the last time I did an interview for them?
我说我自己写了不少台词  编剧抓狂了
I said I write a lot of my own lines, the writers got mad...
让我的角色摔下了电梯间
and made my character fall down the elevator shaft.
谁知道这次我会说什么
So who knows what I might say this time.
要是你脑子里有种东西
If only there was something in your head
能控制你说的每句话就好了
to control the things you say.
少来了  这次你会表现得很好
Come on, Joey, you'll totally keep it in check this time.
而且这种宣传造势
And plus, you know the publicity
对你的事业也很有帮助
would be really good for your career.
这是你应得的
You deserve that.
在专访里  你可以提到
And if you do the interview, you could mention,
"女性朋友瑞秋·格林"
I don't know, "gal pal Rachel Green."
"女性朋友"的意思是失败者吗
Is that "gal pal" spelled LOSER?
好吧  别听他的  拜托
Okay, don't listen to him. Please?
好吧  我接受采访
Fine, all right, I'll do it.
但你们都得坐在旁边
But you guys have to be at the next table
我要是开始说蠢话  就及时阻止我
so you can stop me if I start to say something stupid.
你只指专访时还是一辈子
Just then, or all the time?
因为我们还得去上班
Because we have jobs, you know?
我们会一直在场的  但你得记住
We'll be there for you the whole time. Just remember:
女性朋友瑞秋·格林
Gal pal, Rachel Green.
我要上《肥皂剧文摘》了
I'm gonna be in Soap Opera Digest!
不只是上那个愚蠢的字谜游戏
And not just in the dumb crossword puzzle.
我真的以你为荣
Seriously, proud of you.
《老友记》  第八季  第19集  乔伊接受采访
Friends S08E19 The One With Joey’s Interview
谢谢你抽空接受访问
I really appreciate you taking the time to do this.
别客气  我很乐意
Not at all. Happy to do it.
你们觉得我们做得很明显吗
You think we're being obvious?
不  我们只是四个脖子有问题
No. We're just four people with neck problems,
说话不正常的人
who talk like this.
约在这里见面实在不错
I think it's great you wanted to meet here.
大多数人听说餐费会由杂志社来买单
When most people hear the magazine's paying for it,
都会约到高级大餐厅
they want a big, fancy restaurant.
我真的不知道杂志社会买单
Actually, I didn't know the magazine was paying.
那不重要
Wouldn't have mattered.
我这么做是为了影迷  不是为了白吃
I do this for the fans, not the free food.
你们要点些什么  咖啡
Can I get you anything?  I'll have a cup of coffee.
各种松饼统统来一份
And I'll have all the muffins.
我们不能说话
We're not talking.
终于可以不说话了
Oh, finally.
根据你的个人资料
So according to your bio,
在《我们的日子》之前你做过很多工作
you've done quite a bit of work before Days of Our Lives.
哪份工作尤其令你自豪
Anything that you're particularly proud of?
你想要的只不过是个小弟
All you want is a dingle
你所嫉妒的是男人的老二
What you envy's a shwang
它可以用来撒尿
A thing through which you can tinkle
时而拿来玩弄  时而让其悬空摇摆
Or play with, or simply let hang
各位  你们遇到过这种情况吗
Folks, has this ever happened to you?
你打开冰箱  想喝杯牛奶
You go to the refrigerator to get a nice glass of milk,
但纸盒很难打开
and these darn cartons are so flingin'flangin' hard to open.
天啊  你说得对  麦克
Boy, you said it, Mike.
一定有更棒的办法  没错  凯文
There's gotta be a better way!  And there is, Kevin!
这是他第一次使用这样产品
This is the first time he's ever used this product,
你们会看到使用方法有多简单  来吧
you're gonna see how easy this is to do. Go ahead.
这适用于所有牛奶纸盒  确实简单
This works in any milk can'ton.  It is easy.
现在我每天都能喝牛奶了
Now I can have milk every day.
就这样了吗  维克多
So this is it, Victor?
我猜是吧  所以
Yeah, I guess it is. And so...
我要搭上这艘太空船
...I'm gonna get on this spaceship...
到巴拉根七号星寻找替代能源
...and I'm gonna go to Blargon 7 in search of alternative fuels.
但两百年后我再回来
But when I return 200 years from now,
你早已经不在
you'll be long gone.
我却一点都不会变老
But I won't have aged at all.
你得要你的曾曾孙女来找我
So you tell your greatgreat granddaughter to look me up.
因为  艾德莉恩
Because, Adrian...
宝贝
...baby...
我想见见她
...I'm gonna want to meet her.
我出现了  我要来修复印机
Okay, here I come. Here I come. See I'm coming to fix the copier.
我没办法靠近复印机
I can't get to the copier.
心想"我该怎么办"
I'm thinking, "What do I do? What do I do?"
所以我就看着他们做爱
So I just watch them have sex.
然后我说...  等一下  我要说台词了
And then I say... Wait, here's my line:
你知道吗  那样会把纸匣弄坏
You know, that's bad for the paper tray.
干得漂亮  朋友  谢谢
Nice work, my friend.  Thank you.
等一下  我又出现了
Wait, you see me again.
等一下  那家伙的屁股挡到我了
Hang on, the guy's butt's blocking me.
我出现了  我出现了  我出现了
There I am. There I am. There I am.
我做过太多工作  只选一个真的很难
There are so many things, it's hard to pick just one.
我要去买咖啡  你们需要什么东西吗
I'm gonna get some coffee, anyone want anything?
我要蓝莓松饼跟甘菊茶
Yeah. I'd actually love s blueberry muffin and chamomile tea.
双份拿铁  多加奶泡
Double latte. Extra foam.
我要百吉饼加...  我只是礼貌性问一下
A bagel with only...  I was just being polite.
你不工作的时候呢
Okay. How about when you're not working?
你在业余时间都做些什么
What do you do in your spare time?
快看这个蠢货
Look at this clown.
仗着自己的船大
Just because he's got a bigger boat
就以为整条河都是他的
he thinks he can take up the whole river.
别挡路  混蛋
Get out of the way, jackass!
谁会把自己的船取名为"海岸警卫队"呢
Who names their boat Coast Guard, anyway?
他们就是海岸警卫队
That is the Coast Guard.
他们在这里做什么
What are they doing out here?
海岸在那边
The coast is all the way over there!
快看啊  太不可思议了
Check it out. This is unbelievable.
乔伊已经憋气快四分钟了
Joey has been holding his breath for almost four minutes.
哥们  你想害死我吗
Dude, are you trying to kill me?
看来  今天你真的很忙
Well, I see you've had a very productive day.
这项牛仔帽太过了吧
Isn't the cowboy hat a little much?
来吧  真的很好玩
Come on, it's fun!
好吧
All right.
这不是女人的帽子吗
Isn't this a woman's hat?
别说傻话了  快去帮我们泡荼
Dude, stop talking crazy and make us some tea.
我们得把黄片关掉
You know what? We have to turn off the porn.
你说得对
I think you're right.
好吧  准备好了吗  一
All right, ready?  One.
二  三  三
Two, three.  Three.
感觉不错
That's kind of nice.
我松了一口气  对
It's kind of a relief.  Yeah.
你想看看我们还能收到吗  好啊
You wanna see if we still have it?  Yeah.
我们有免费的黄片看
Free porn! We have free porn here!
我在业余时间会念书给盲人听
In my spare time, I read to the blind.
我还是孩子们的曼陀珠
And I'm also a mento for kids.
曼陀珠  曼陀珠  榜样
A mento?  You know, a mento. A role model.
曼陀珠  对
A mento?  Right.
你说的是（喜欢）糖果吗
Like the candy?
没错  我很喜欢
As a matter of fact, I do.
读者一直都想知道肥皂剧明星
Another thing that our readers always want to know
是怎么保持健美身材的
is how soap stars stay in such great shape.
你有健身妙方吗
Do you have a fitness regime?
明星们会正确地饮食  伴以大量运动
We stars usually just try to eat right and get lots of exercise.
你知道我们已经丢了一小时的球
You realize that we've been throwing this ball,
都一直没掉吗
without dropping it for an hour?
真的吗
Are you serious?
半小时前我就发现了
Yeah. I realized it about a halfhour ago
但我不想说出来
but I didn't want to say anything,
怕自己乌鸦嘴
'cause I didn't want to jinx it.
我们真的很厉害  对
Wow, we are pretty good at this.  Yeah.
我们忘了吃午餐
Hey, we totally forgot about lunch.
这是我第一次忘了吃饭
I think that's the first time I've ever missed a meal.
我的裤子都松了
My pants are a little loose.
你怎么了
What's wrong with you?
我举重的时候
I got this blinding pain in my stomach
肚子突然痛得要命
when I was lifting weights before.
后来我昏了过去
And then I passed out.
然后就一直站不起来了
I haven't been able to stand up since.
但我觉得没什么大问题
But I don't think it's anything serious.
听起来像是疝气  快去看医生吧
Sounds like a hernia. Go to the doctor.
不行  如果我去看医生
No way! If I go to the doctor for anything,
就得把这玩意从我肚子里取出来
it's gonna be for this thing sticking out of my stomach!
我为什么要恢复健身的习惯呢
Why'd I have to start working out again?
该死的15磅哑铃
Damn you, fifteens!
这是什么  松糕  有好几层
What is it?  A trifle. It's got all of these layers.
先是一层手指饼干  然后一层果酱
First there's a layer of ladyfingers, then a layer of jam,
然后是奶油冻  是我自己亲手做的哦
then custard, which I made from scratch.
黑莓  手指饼干  豌豆洋葱烩牛肉
Raspberries, more ladyfingers, beef sauteed with peas and onions.
再加一层奶油冻
Then a little bit more custard.
味道好像臭脚丫
It tastes like feet.
我喜欢
I like it.
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
这有什么不好的  奶油冻  好吃
What's not to like? Custard, good.
果酱  好吃  肉  好吃
Jam, good. Meat, good!
你的脸色不太好  乔伊
Well, you don't look good, Joe.
冰箱坏了  我得把所有东西吃掉
Well, the fridge broke, so I had to eat everything.
冷盘  冰淇淋  酸橙
Cold cuts, ice cream, limes.
那个棕色罐子里装了什么
Hey, what was in that brown jar?
还放在冰箱里呢  现在没了
That's still in there?  Not anymore.
这一块没有沾到地板
This piece doesn't have floor on it.
别越界  少来了
Stick to your side.  Hey, come on, now.
好吧  你们吃什么呢
All right, what are we having?
我不相信那些疯狂的节食法
I don't believe in these crazy diets.
只要正常饮食就行了
Just everything in moderation.
你的松饼来了
Your muffins.
我要外带
I'll take those to go.
给孩子们吃
For the kids.
我知道我想问什么了
I know what I wanted to ask you.
多年前  编剧安排你在剧中意外身亡
You were on the show years ago and then they killed you off.
那是怎么回事
What happened there?
说起来很傻
It was so stupid,
我在一次访问中说了不该说的话
I said some stuff in an interview I shouldn't have said.
但今天我不会那么做  了解
But believe me, that's not gonna happen today.  Understood.
你那时说了什么  我说我...
So, what'd you say back then?  I said that I...
嘿  乔伊  你好吗
Hey, Joey!  How you doing?
她是雪丽
You guys, this is Shelly.
她在代表《肥皂剧文摘》访问我
She's interviewing me for Soap Opera Digest.
雪丽  他们是我的朋友
Shelly, these are my friends.
嗨  我是女性朋友瑞秋·格林
Hi, I'm gal pal Rachel Green.
你想知道八卦消息就来找我
And if you want the dirt, I'm the one you come too.
这可能是乔伊的孩子  谁知道呢
This might be Joey's baby, who knows?
我只是在开玩笑  我是女性朋友瑞秋·格林
I'm just kidding. Seriously, gal pal Rachel Green.
她刚刚丢够了她还没有出世的孩子的脸
Who just lost the respect of her unborn child.
我去把这个热一下
I'm gonna go get this warmed up.
乔伊  你表现得很好
Joey, you're doing great.
到目前为止没有说傻话
So far, nothing stupid.
曼陀珠  不用  谢谢
Mento?  No, thanks.
身为乔伊的朋友
So as Joey's friends,
你们有什么事想跟读者分享吗
is there anything that you guys think our readers should know?
没有  他是个大好人
No, just that he is a great guy.
说这种话你也想上《肥皂剧文摘》
That'll get you into Soap Opera Digest.
我...
Well, I...
我想说  乔伊
I'd just like to say that Joey...
真的丰富了我们的生活
...truly has enriched the days of our lives.
谁也想不到这么性感的男人还会那么体贴
I think that you don't expect someone so hot to be so sweet.
这句我喜欢  你叫什么名字  菲比·布非
I like that. What's your name?  Phoebe Buffay.
怎么拼  我们要保证拼写正确
How do you spell that? So we can get it right.
菲比的P  希比的H
Okay, it's P as in Phoebe. H as in Heebie.
欧比的O  艾比的E  比的B
O as in Obie. E as in Ebie. B as in Beebee.
E是"哈喽  朋友"
And E as in, "'ello there, mate!"
太棒了  很高兴能认识你们
Great. It was nice meeting all of you.
对  我也是  谢谢
Yeah, you too.  Thanks.
你似乎有很多朋友
So it seems you have a lot of friends.
谁是你最好的朋友
Who would you say is your best friend?
你为什么会有两个
How come you have two?
这个是送你的
Well, this one's for you.
少来了  不  我做不到
Get out!  No, I can't.
我知道这对你来说意义重大
No, no. Listen, I, I know how much this means to you
这不只是首饰而己
and I also know that this is about more than just jewelry,
它代表了
It's about you and me
你跟我是最好的朋友
and the fact that we're best buds.
这是友谊吗  我想是的
Is this friendship? I think so!
你看  我们是手镯兄弟
Check it out! We're bracelet buddies!
他们以后就会这么称呼我们
That's what they'll call us!
乔伊  对不起  没关系  别担心
Joey, I'm sorry.  It's all right. Don't worry about it.
可是你看啊  会留下印子
No, but look, that's gonna leave a stain.
瑞秋  没关系  你在乔伊家
Rach, hey, it's fine. You're at Joey's.
真的吗  对  你看
Really?  Yeah, look.
我从没过过这种生活  我知道
I've never lived like this before.  I know!
别浪费  这毕竟还是食物  天啊
Well, don't waste it. I mean, it's still food. Jeez!
我对这件事有深深的罪恶感
I've been feeling incredibly guilty about this,
我想当个好朋友  我本来就是个好朋友
because I wanna be a good friend and damn it, I am a good friend.
闭上你的嘴巴跟眼睛
So just shut up and close your eyes.
你确实是个好朋友
You are a good friend.
我今天早上去试镜  但我失败了
The audition was this morning, and I didn't get it.
但那个吻真的很棒  瑞秋真是个幸运的姑娘
But that was a hell of a kiss. Rachel is a very lucky girl.
请参赛者离开隔离间
Let's get the contestants out of their isolation booths.
出发
And they're off!
别挡住我的选手  裁判
Get your foot off my contestant! Judge!
裁判判决  没有犯规
Judge rules: No violation.
鸭子找到花生酱饼干了
The duck gets the Nutter Butter!
不  那不是花生酱饼干  那是以前掉的馄饨
No! That's not a NutterButter, that's just an old Wonton!
裁判判决是花生酱饼干
Judge rules: Nutter Butter!
黑哨
Tough call.
我在探索频道看到过
I'd seen this thing on The Discovery Channel.
等一下  我看过那期节目
Wait a minute. I saw that!
在探索频道上
On The Discovery Channel.
关于水母  如果你...
Yeah, about jellyfish, and how if you...
你往自己身上尿尿了
You peed on yourself?
别那么说  你不了解那有多痛
You can't say that! You don't know!
我以为我会痛得昏过去
I thought I'd pass out from the pain.
总之我试过了  但我没办法那样子弯曲身子
Anyway, I tried, but I couldn't bend that way.
所以
So...
没错  我挺身而出了
That's right, I stepped up!
她是我的朋友  她需要帮忙
She's my friend and she needed help!
有必要的话  我可以往你们任何人身上尿尿
If I had to, I'd pee on any one of you!
不  我没有最好的朋友
Nope. No best friend.
我只有很多密友
Just a lot of close friends.
现在回到那部剧
So now back to the show.
有那么多男同志支持你  你有什么感觉
How does it feel to have a huge gay fan base?
真的吗  我
Really? Me?
我都不认识任何男同志
Wow, I don't even know any huge gay people.
我真的觉得心好痛
It hurts me. It physically hurts me.
这是我们的私下谈话  你不是...
Now, off the record, you're not...
怎么  你是在说我的男士背包吗
What? Are you referring to my man's bag?
刚开始我只觉得它好看  但它还很实用
At first, I thought it just looked good, but it's practical, too.
快看啊  里面有很多放东西的小袋子
Check it out. It's got compartments for stuff:
你可以放皮夹  钥匙  通讯簿
Your wallet, your keys, your address book.
化妆品
Your makeup.
我是要从你的正面滑下去  让我们面对面
No, no, no. Should I climb down your front so we're face to face
还是从你的背面滑下去
or should I climb down your back
屁股对着脸
so we're butt to face?
我想面对面比较好  对  面对面
I think face to face. Face to face, yeah.  I would say that.
好吧  我来了  好吧
Okay, here I come.  All right.
天啊...你有多重  罗斯
Oh, my... How much do you weigh, Ross?
我现在不想回答那个问题
I prefer not to answer that right now.
假日结束后  我胖了不少
I'm still carrying a little holiday weight.
我们说"面对面"的时候
You know when we talked about "face to face,"
没有完全想清楚
we didn't think it all the way through!
菲比
Hey, Pheebs.
你看
Check it out.
我很有男子气概吧
How much of a man am I?
不错嘛  男子气概中透着淫荡
Nice. Manly and also kind of a slut.
你变成女人了
You're turning into a woman.
才没有  你为什么会那么说  那太伤人了
No, I'm not! Why would you say that? That's just mean!
我惹毛你了吗  我说了什么
Now I've upset you? What did I say?
不是你说的话  而是你的语气
Not what you said, it's just the way you said it.
天啊  我是个女人
Oh, my God! I'm a woman!
我睡得很香  没错
Great nap.  It really was.
我  男同志  不是
Me? Gay? No. No. No.
但我有很多密友是男同志
But I have a number of close friends who are.
我们来谈谈女人
So let's talk about women.
我相信女性读者对你的爱情生活
I'm sure our female readers will be interested
很有兴趣
to know about your romantic life.
我会对着一个女人上下打量  对她说
What I do is, I look a woman up and down and I say:
"嘿  你好吗"
"Hey. How you doing?"
拜托
Oh, please.
嘿  你好吗
Hey. How you doing?
他有一辆很棒的保时捷
He has an amazing Porsche under there.
我很乐意让你们参观
I'd love to show you, but...
但我才刚把它停好  它在休息
I just tucked her in. She's sleeping.
你们两个想去喝一杯吗
Would you two girls like to go for a drink?
瑞秋在吗  我是她妹妹  天啊  吉尔
Is Rachel here? I'm her sister.  Oh, my God! Jill!
天啊  瑞秋  嗨
Oh, my God! Rachel!  Oh, hi!
天啊  快帮我们介绍  他是钱德勒
Oh, my God! Introduce us!  Well, this is Chandler.
你认识莫妮卡跟罗斯
You know Monica and Ross.
她是菲比  他是乔伊
That's Phoebe. That's Joey.
嘿  你好吗  少来
Hey, how you doing?  Don't!
你是个好人
You're a really nice guy.
我很愿意当你的室友跟朋友
I'm happy to be your roommate and your friend.
我只是对你没有那种感觉
I'm just... You know, I just don't feel that way about you.
我知道是怎么回事了
I see what happened.
那是因为我试着抗拒你  对吧
It's because I was trying to repel you. Right?
相信我  我发动攻势后
Believe me, you'd feel a lot different
你会有截然不同的感觉
if I turned it on.
我觉得不会  绝对会
I don't think so.  Oh, I do.
你好吗
How you doing?
我很好
I'm okay.
什么  天啊
What? Oh, dear God!
没什么好说的  我真的很害羞
Not much to tell there. I'm really shy.
好了  我猜我已经问完了
So that's it. I guess that's all I need.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
我想应该下一期就会刊出你的访问
I think they will be running this in the beginning of next month.
太棒了  谢谢你
Oh, great. Great. Thank you.
再见  拜拜
Bye.  Byebye.
我办到了  太棒了
I did it.  Amazing.
等一下  我差点忘了
Wait, I almost forgot.
我们对每个人都要提这个问题
We have to ask everybody this:
除了《我们的日子》以外你最喜欢哪出肥皂剧
Other than Days, what's your favorite soap opera?
我不看肥皂剧  抱歉
Oh, I don't watch soap operas. Excuse me?
我的生活没那么无聊
I have a life, you know?
谢谢  《肥皂剧文摘》的读者
Thank you. The readers at Soap Opera Digest
知道那点一定会很高兴
will be happy to learn that.
非常好
Good enough.
只差一点而己
So close.
他们竟然没登出你
I can't believe they didn't put in the part
说你不看肥皂剧那一段
where you said you didn't watching soaps.
我打电话告诉那个女记者  我是在开玩笑
Yeah, I called the lady about that. I told her I was just joking.
她接受了
She was nice about it.
你跟她上床了  对吧  可以那么说
You slept with her, didn't you?  A little bit.
你的这张照片英气逼人啊
This picture of you is steamy.
那是为了配合我男同志影迷的喜好
That's just a little something for my huge gay fan base.
你在对我抛媚眼吗
Did you just wink at me?
是你说喜欢那张照片的
You're the one who loves the picture.